http://www.charter.com.au/privacy

Navigation
Charter privacy policy
Charter Financial Planning Limited (Charter) understands that privacy is important to its clients. Being part of the AMP Group means we are subject to the principles outlined within their Privacy Policy (The Privacy Policy) which we have adopted from 10 March 2014. Please click here to download a copy of The Privacy Policy .
If you have come through to this page from your financial adviser's website, your financial adviser is authorised by Charter and is also subject to The Privacy Policy.
The Privacy Policy explains how we comply with the Australian Privacy Principles, which have been established under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). The Privacy Policy covers:
why we need to collect your personal information
the types of personal information we collect, and how it is collected
how we protect your personal information, and who it could be disclosed to
specific issues relating to privacy and the use of the internet.
Contacting Charter about privacy
We always welcome feedback about client experiences, as we know things don't always go the way they should. If you:
have a general enquiry about how personal information is collected or used
would like to access or update your personal information
wish to make a complaint relating to privacy
you can contact us directly as set out below. We are committed to doing the right thing by you and we will respond as soon as possible.
The AMP Privacy Officer
PO Box 300
Parramatta NSW 2124
Telephone: 1300 157 173
Alternatively your concerns can be emailed to: askamp@amp.com.au
Close
